https://www.modcloth.com/privacy

Help Center HomeU.S. Shipping & ReturnsInternational InfoMy Account & OrdersSizing & ProductsCommunity & ContestsUnsubscribe & CatalogsHomeModCloth PoliciesPrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyModCloth Privacy Policy
Last Updated:
September 3rd, 2020 About ModCloth
Since ModCloth’s breakout in 2002 as an indie brand that championed a vintage, feminine, and fun fashion aesthetic, ModCloth prides itself on having a unique product assortment and mission to empower and uplift women through their brand values. About This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy explains how ModCloth collects, shares, and uses any information that relates to you when you use our Websites, engage with us on social media, or otherwise interact with us (your “Personal Data”) as well information we collect from vendors, suppliers, services providers, employees, and contractors. This Privacy Policy also explains the rights you have concerning the Personal Data that we process and how you can exercise these rights. If you are a vendor, supplier, service provider, employee or contractor, how we handle your personal information is set out in our agreement with you or our employee policies. This policy will explain: What personal information does ModCloth collect from your use of our Websites and your direct interactions with us?What personal information does ModCloth collect from third parties?How does ModCloth use your personal information?With whom does ModCloth share your personal information?How does ModCloth secure your personal information?What choices do you have regarding the collection, use, and distribution of your personal information?How can you contact us with questions or concerns? What Personal Information Does ModCloth Collect?
ModCloth collects personal information from its customers, visitors to our Websites, connections on social media, service providers, suppliers, job applicants, and others who interact with us. We additionally collect a variety of information from third parties.
What Personal Information does ModCloth collect from your interactions with us?
ModCloth requests and collects a variety of personal information from our customers to deliver the products and services you request and to help improve your shopping experience.
We collect information from you directly when you provide it to us in the course of a transaction between you and ModCloth.
We also collect it or when you otherwise volunteer information to us by purchasing products online, sharing photos with us, participating in our contests, scheduling consultations, or otherwise interacting with us. The information we collect this way often includes: NameAge and date of birthShipping and billing addressesGenderEmail address or telephone numberPayment information such as your credit or debit card numbersItems in your shopping cartOrder and purchase history information, such as the products you have bought, or returnedNotes or gift messages you add to your orderAccount information, if you choose to create an accountMeasurements including height, weight, shoe size, and bra sizeInformation you supply to us when you use a ModStylist including your wedding date, style preferences, hobbies, and body typeIndividual preferences and characteristics, such as inferences related to shopping patterns and behaviorsEmployment information, such as occupation, title, licenses and professional memberships Education information, such as degree and schooling informationPreferences on our products including items you’ve “loved” or put on your wishlistReviews of our products Other information provided in online formsRecordings of chats, phone calls, or other audio and video recordings.Location information, such as geo-location informationDevice and online identifiers and related information such as cookie IDs and browser visitsSocial media profile and related information when you interact with us on an outside social media website.Photos if you choose to share them with us Our legal basis for collecting this information is to fulfill a transaction you request, through your consent, when you consent to share non-transactional information with us, or because of our legitimate business interest. Employees and Contractors
If you are an employee or contractor of ModCloth, how we handle your personal information is set out in our employment agreement with you as well as in our employee policies and employee handbook.
Vendors, Suppliers and Service Providers
If you are a vendor, supplier or service provider of ModCloth, how we handle your personal information is set out in the contractual agreements we have with you. Information That You Provide to Us About Others
You may provide ModCloth with personal information about other people, such as their name and email address. When you purchase a Gift Certificate for another individual, we will use their name and email address to send them a one-time email.
We use this information for the sole purpose of completing your request. We do not share your friend’s email information for any other purposes unless that friend creates a membership to ModCloth. ModCloth stores this information for the sole purpose of fulling the gift card. This individual may contact us at support@modcloth.com to request that we remove this information from our database. What Information Does ModCloth Collect Automatically?
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include, for example, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, or clickstream data.
We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve marketing, analytics, and site functionality.
Tracking Technologies
When you interact with ModCloth.com, we use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts to collect information about you. We use these technologies in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site, and gathering demographic information about you and our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies on an individual as well as an aggregated basis.
We use cookies for many different functions, including user authentication, our shopping cart, and to customize the user experience. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still browse our site, but your ability to use most features or areas of our Websites may be limited. Our Cookie Policy provides more information.
Click here
Local Storage Objects (HTML5)
We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information.
Various browsers may offer management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. Do Not Track
Do Not Track is a voluntary program among Internet advertisers that gives users the ability to opt-out of behavioral targeting and advertising through Internet browser settings.
At this time, we do not respond to “do not track” settings. What Personal Information Does ModCloth Collect From Third Parties? Website Traffic
When you visit our Websites, we automatically collect some information about you, including your IP address, browser type, and device used to access our Websites. We may receive additional information about you from Google Analytics that can be associated with your IP address, including the pages you visited, how you reached our Websites, and demographic information. We use this information to help us better understand how people are accessing our Websites and to improve our Websites.
You may prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on our Websites by deleting or disabling cookies from our sites. If you do not want Google Analytics to share your information, you may install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. For more information, see the Google Analytics opt-out webpage. Social Media
When you interact with us on social media websites, such as Facebook and Instagram, we may collect information relating to your interactions with us (such as items you have “liked”) and profile information you have chosen to make public. If you wish to restrict access to your social media profiles, you may change your settings on the social media provider’s website. Job Applicant Information
We may engage with you on LinkedIn as part of our hiring process and collect information related to your interactions with us as well as profile information you have chosen to make public.
This includes information you voluntarily provide to us, including your name, physical address, email address, resume, cover letter, age/date of birth, telephone number, citizenship, background check which may include criminal records, employment status and, if you are extended an offer to work with us, your social security number. We will use this information solely to assess your qualifications, to contact you regarding the application process, and to manage your application. If you wish to restrict access to your LinkedIn profile, you may change your settings on the social media provider’s website. Referrals
You may be referred to us when an acquaintance enters your email address or other contact information on our Websites or purchases a gift card on your behalf.
You can find out more about your rights in this privacy policy. How Does ModCloth Use Your Personal Information?
We use your personal information to provide
products and service, to process your transaction, send you promotional messages about products or services we think you might like, improve our Websites, product offerings, and services, understand your preferences, promote our products to others, provide you with style tips, provide customer service, and to improve our overall relationship with you.
We may use this information, also, for other legitimate business purposes, including maintaining records on your transaction for legal, tax, and compliance purposes, fraud prevention, or marketing.
How Long Does ModCloth Keep Your Personal Information?
We will keep your personal information for at least as long as is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected.
If you have an account with us, we will keep your account information 5 years from the last activity in their account. We may retain your information after the purposes for which it was collected fulfilled as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, protect our assets, and enforce our agreements.
Who Does ModCloth Share Your Personal Information With?
We may share information from all of the categories of personal information that we collect with other companies for a business purpose.
We provide your personal information to third-party service providers that perform business tasks on our behalf. These include email marketing providers, payment processors, cloud storage providers, offsite electronic backups, shipping and logistics providers, and other providers of compliance verification, rewards program management, referral program administration, customer relationship management, hiring, and enterprise management. Personal information that we share with third-parties is subject to contractual clauses to ensure the protection of your data to the extent allowable by law.
We may also share information with other third parties as required by law.
Payment Processing
ModCloth uses third-party payment processors such as PayPal to facilitate the purchase of our products. Storage and Business Logistics
Additionally, we use third-party logistics and shipping agents such as DHL to ensure the payment and delivery of your purchased products. We use a variety of third-party providers such to store and process your personal information. Account and Relationship Management
We use account and customer management software such as Kustomer to manage our account information and assist in customer service. Advertising and Marketing
We use services such as PebblePost to advertise directly to you through email or to manage our advertising on other sites.
Social Media
We may share information about you with Social Media services like Instagram.
Hiring
We use job sites such as LinkedIn to help with the hiring of new employees. If you wish to restrict access to your LinkedIn profile, you may change your settings on the social media provider’s website. Legal Requirements
We may also share your information with the government, law enforcement agencies, or other third parties under certain circumstances where they have made a formal request (such as in responding to a court order, subpoena, or judicial proceeding) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, or when disclosure is required for the establishment of defenses or claims in any legal action or dispute involving ModCloth or any of its officers, directors, employees, agents, contractors, and partners, or to consummate a corporate transaction such as an assignment of assets. How Does ModCloth Secure Your Personal Information?
ModCloth recognizes the importance of maintaining the security of our customers’ personal information.
ModCloth maintains technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information against loss, misuse, or unauthorized access. Security measures we use to protect your personal information include physical and technical security access controls or other safeguards, information security technologies and policies, procedures to help ensure the appropriate disposal of information, and training programs.
If you have any questions about security on our Websites, the systems on which we store your personal information, or other security measures we have in place, you can contact us at support@modcloth.com.
What choices are available to you regarding ModCloth’s collection, use, and distribution of your personal information?
Your Data Rights Generally
You may contact us at any time with questions about this privacy statement or if you wish to exercise any rights you may have in your personal information.
Subject to any legal, regulatory, or contractual obligations we may have, we will answer your request as soon as possible and in no more than one month from the time we receive your request. If your request is particularly complicated, we may extend this period up to an additional two months. To make a request, you may contact us using the information provided below. If you have an account with us, you may make changes to your personal information by logging in to your account and making changes there. If you wish to unsubscribe from marketing communications, you may click the “unsubscribe” button in these communications. Children
ModCloth is intended for users who are 16 years of age and older. If you are under the age of 16, you are not permitted to submit any personal information to ModCloth. If you believe we may have collected information from a person under the age of 16, please promptly contact support@modcloth.com so we can correct it. Your California Data Rights
If you reside in California, our use of your information is governed by California law, including the California Privacy Protection Act (CCPA). This section applies only to California residents. Personal Information Collected and Purposes of Use
We collect and use information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, to you or your devices when you visit our Websites, provide us your personal information, or have a contractual or business relationship with us or any of our customers, (“Personal Information”).
We collect Personal Information for the purposes identified in the section above called: “What Data Does ModCloth Collect?”.
We may have shared your Personal Information with the categories of third parties identified in the section above called: “Who Does ModCloth Share Your Data With?”.
Unless specifically stated, we do not share, disclose, or sell personal information to third parties for their use, but we do share your personal information with our trusted partners to support our business. In these arrangements, the use of the information we share is limited by policies, contracts, or similar restrictions. Your Privacy Rights under California Law
Californians have the following rights regarding our collection and use of your personal information. We may ask you to provide additional information to verify your request.
Californians have the right to request the information regarding the personal information we have collected, sold, or disclosed about you.
This policy explains the Categories of personal information collected about you, and sources from which collected;Our purpose for collecting personal information;Categories of third parties with which the personal information was shared; andSpecific pieces of personal information collected about consumers.Categories of your personal information sold in the preceding 12 months;Categories of third parties to whom your personal information has been disclosed;Categories of personal information that we disclosed about consumers for a business purpose.
If this Policy does not answer your questions, then you have the right to contact us and request further information on each of these topics. Right to Opt-out
Californians have the right to opt-out of sharing, disclosure, or sale of your Personal Information.
To exercise this right, you or your authorized representative may submit a request by clicking on this link:
DO NOT SELL MY PERSONAL INFORMATION
Right to Request Deletion
Californians have the right to request that we delete the personal information we have about you. However, we are not required to delete information if it is necessary to retain your information to:Complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, provide a good or service requested by you, or a transaction reasonably anticipated within the context of our or one of our affiliate’s ongoing business relationship with you, or to otherwise perform a contract we have with you.Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity or prosecute those responsible for that activity.Debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right of free speech, or exercise another right provided for by law.Facilitate solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations based on your relationship with us or one of our affiliates.Comply with a legal obligation.Otherwise use the personal information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which it was provided. Contact Us
You can contact us with questions about this Privacy Notice for California Residents or to exercise your rights as described in this Notice.
Telephone number: Email: support@modcloth.com with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the body and subject line of the email
Weblinks: CCPA Request and DO NOT SELL MY PERSONAL INFORMATION
Your Nevada Data Rights
If you reside in Nevada, our use of your information is governed by Nevada law. This section applies only to Nevada residents. Personal Information Collection and Purposes of UseWe collect certain personal information of Nevada consumers as identified in the section above called: “Information Collected.” We collect this personal information for the purposes identified in the section above called “What Personal Information does ModCloth collect from your interactions with us?”
Your Privacy Rights
You have the right to access and correct your personal information or opt-out of the sale of personal information. If you would like to review, correct, or update your personal information, you or your authorized representative may submit your request to support@modcloth.com.
We will respond to your verified request as soon as reasonably practicable, but no later than sixty (60) days after receipt. If circumstances cause any delay in our response, you will be promptly notified and provided a date for our response. We generally do not disclose or share personal information for profit. Under Nevada law, you have the right to direct us to not sell or license your personal information to third parties. To exercise this right, if applicable, you or your authorized representative may submit a request to support@modcloth.com.
We will respond to your verified request as soon as reasonably practicable, but no later than sixty (60) days after receipt. If circumstances cause any delay in our response, you will be promptly notified and provided a date for our response. Contact US
You can contact us with questions about our handling of Nevada residents’ data or exercise your rights as a Nevada resident by contacting us at support@modcloth.com.. Data Rights for those in the European Economic Area(EEA), United Kingdom(UK), and Switzerland
If you reside in the EEA, the United Kingdom, or Switzerland, our use of your personal information is governed by the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation, or “GDPR” or applicable EEA, UK or Swiss law. These grant you particular rights in your personal information, including the right to alter, correct, receive, or delete personal information stored by ModCloth at any time, subject to our business interests and any legal requirements we may face.
Many of these rights are extended to all of our customers as a courtesy and we list them in the “What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use, and distribution of your personal information?” section of this statement.
Those in the EEA, UK, or Switzerland have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA are available here. We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights under applicable data protection laws. To protect your privacy and security, we may need to take reasonable steps to verify your identity before responding to your request. To exercise any of these rights, you may contact us at dsupport@ModCloth.com. If we are unable to resolve your complaint, you may contact your country’s data protection authority. Those in the EAA, UK, or Switzerland wishing to contact our GDPR Article 27 representative in the European Union or the United Kingdom may contact us at modcloth@gdprrepresentative.eu or modcloth@privacyrep.co.uk
Data Transfers to the United States
When you chose to do business with ModCloth your personal data is transferred to the United States for processing.
The laws of the United States do not protect your personal data to the same extent or in the same way as in your own country.
To the fullest extent allowed by applicable law, you voluntarily request and consent to the trans-border transfer and hosting of such information to fulfill a transaction request or perform as part of a contract. How you can contact us with any questions or concerns Contact Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or wish to exercise any rights in your personal information, you may contact our privacy team at support@modcloth.com or you may contact us by mail or by phone at: +1-888-495-9699 Updates to this Privacy Policy
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to changing legal, technical or business developments. When we update our Privacy Policy, we will take appropriate measures to inform you, consistent with the significance of the changes we make. We will obtain your consent to any material Privacy Policy changes if and where applicable data protection laws require this.
You can see when this Privacy Policy was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the top of this Privacy Policy.OUR COOKIE POLICY SUMMARYThis cookie policy explains what cookies are and how ModCloth ("we", "us" or "our") uses them on our websites (our "site").
We encourage you to read the policy in full so that you can understand what information we collect using cookies and how that information is used. You can usually change the settings of your browser to modify the permissions you give to us and third parties for the storing of and gaining access to cookies on your device. WHAT ARE COOKIES?Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information, which are downloaded to your browsing device (such as a computer, tablet, or smartphone) when you visit a website.
Cookies can be recognized by the website that downloaded them, or other websites that use the same cookies.
This helps websites know if the browsing device has visited them before. WHAT ARE COOKIES USED FOR?Cookies do lots of different jobs, like helping us understand how our website is being used, letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improving your browsing experience.
Cookies can also help ensure marketing you see online is more relevant to you and your interests. WHAT TYPES OF COOKIES DO WE USE?The types of cookies used on our site fall into one of the following categories: strictly necessary; analytics; functionality; advertising; and social media. You can find out more about each of the cookie categories in the table below. StrictlyNecessary CookiesThese cookies are essential to make our site work.
They enable you to move around the site and use its features.
Without these cookies, services that are necessary for you to be able to use our site, such as accessing secure areas, cannot be provided.Analytics CookiesThese cookies collect information about how people are using our site, including which pages are visited the most often, how people are moving from one link to another, and if visitors get error messages from certain pages.
All information these cookies collect is grouped together with information from other people's use of our site on an anonymous basis.
Overall, these cookies provide us with analytical information about how our site is performing and how we can improve it.Functionality CookiesThese cookies allow us to remember choices you make and tailor our site to provide enhanced features and content to you.
For example, these cookies can be used to remember your user name, language choice or country selection, changes you've made to text size or font, and other parts of pages that you can customize.Advertising CookiesThese cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are more relevant to you and your interests.
They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as to help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. This information may be shared with other organizations, such as advertising partners. This means after you have been to our site, you may see some advertisements about our services elsewhere on the internet.Social Media CookiesIn order to enhance your internet experience and make the sharing of content easier, some of the pages on our website may contain tools or applications that are linked to third party social media service providers such as Facebook, Twitter, or Google+. Through these tools or applications, the social media service provider may set its own cookies on your device. We do not control these cookies and you should check the social media service provider's website for further details about how they use cookies. HOW LONG WILL COOKIES STAY ON MY BROWSING DEVICE?The length of time a cookie will stay on your browsing device depends on whether it is a "persistent" or "session" cookie.
Session cookies will only stay on your device until you stop browsing.
Persistent cookies stay on your browsing device after you have finished browsing until they expire or are deleted.
Details of "persistent" and "session" cookies can be found below in the section "Cookies used by ModCloth.” FIRST AND THIRD-PARTY COOKIES"First-party cookies" are cookies that belong to us and that we place on your device. "Third-party cookies" are cookies that another party places on your browsing device when you visit our site.Third parties setting cookies from our website will be providing a service to us or a function of the site, but we do not always control how third-party cookies are used.
You should check the third party's website for more information about how they use cookies.
Details of third parties that set cookies through our website can be found in the section below entitled "Cookies used by ModCloth.” HOW TO MANAGE COOKIES FROM THIS SITEYou can withdraw or modify your consent to our use of cookies at any time.
If you want to withdraw or modify your consent, you can usually use the browser that you are viewing this site through to define the conditions of storing or gaining access to cookies and in particular to enable, disable, or delete cookies.
To do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser.
Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access secure areas of the site, and other parts of the site may also not work properly.You can find out more information about how to change your browser cookie settings at www.allaboutcookies.org.Some third parties may use Advertising Cookies to help gather information about your browsing activity so that they can deliver website advertising to you that is relevant to your interests.
To opt-out from other companies that provide online behavioral advertising services, you can opt-out at the following online advertising industry website:
The Digital Advertising Alliance Website, www.aboutads.info, or the European Digital Advertising Alliance Website, www.youronlinechoices.eu. THE COOKIES USED BY MODCLOTHThe following tables and information set out the cookies which are most frequently used on our site. It also provides details of third parties that set cookies through our site.Strictly necessary cookiesCookie NameFirst or Third Party CookiePersistent or Session CookieCookie Purpose__cfduid3rd29 daysUsed by the content network, Cloudflare to identify trusted web traffic_cq_dnt1stSessionThis opt-out cookie identifies if the visitor has deselected any cookies, trackers, or other audience targeting tools__stripe_mid3rd1 yearThis cookie is necessary for making credit card transactions on the website. The service is provided by stripe.com which allows online transactions without storing any credit card information__stripe_sid3rd1 dayThis cookie is necessary for making credit card transactions on the website. The service is provided by stripe.com which allows online transactions without storing any credit card informationcqcid1stSessionRegister whether the user is logged in. This allows the website owner to make parts of the website inaccessible, based on the user's log-in status.m3rd2 yearsDetermines the device used to access the website. This allows the website to be formatted accordingly.s_fid1st5 yearsStores referral ID if third-party cookies are restricted by opt-out.sid1stSessionPreserves user states across page requestGE_C_HCOUNT1stSessionUsed for AdvertisingGE_CSDK_CB1stSessionUsed for AdvertisingGlobalE_CT_Data1st2 yearsUsed for AdvertisingGlobalE_CT_Data1stPersistentUsed for AdvertisingGlobalE_Data1st6 daysUsed for Advertisinghttps://bshzcwbh.klarnaservice...3rdSessionUsed for Advertisingon/demandware.store/Sites-modcloth-Site/default/__Analytics-Start1stSessionUsed for AdvertisingAnalytics cookiesCookie NameFirst or Third Party CookiePersistent or Session CookieCookie Purpose__cq_uuid1st1 yearRegister statistical data on users’ behavior on the website. Used for internal analytics by the website operator._ga1st2 yearsRegisters a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website._gat3rd1 dayUsed by Google Analytics to throttle request rate.-gid1st1 dayRegisters a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.ab3rd1 yearThis cookie is used by the website’s operator in context with multi-variate testing.
This is a tool used to combine or change content on the website.Dwac_#1stSessionUnclassifiedDwanonymous_UID(32)1st179 daysThis cookie contains a specific ID on the visitor in order to distinguish visitors. The information allows the website to remember visitors’ preferences.s_cc1stSessionUsed to check if the user’s browser supports cookies.S_vi1st2 yearsRegisters a unique ID that identifies the user’s device for return visits.Functionality cookiesCookie NameFirst or Third Party CookiePersistent or Session CookieCookie Purposebc_persist_props1stPersistentRegisters whether the user has made any preference choices, allowing the website to apply these upon re-entry.Advertising cookiesCookie NameFirst or Third Party CookiePersistent or Session CookieCookie Purpose#.gif3rdSessionUsed for Advertising__cq_seg1st29 daysCollects data on visitors. This information is used to assign visitors into segments, making website advertisement more efficient._gcl_au3rd3 monthsUsed by Google AdSense for experimenting with advertisement efficiency across websites using their services._schn1stSessionTracks the individual sessions on the website, allowing the website to compile statistical data from multiple visits. This data can also be used to create leads for marketing purposes._scid1st13 monthsSets a unique ID for the visitor, that allows third party advertisers to target the visitor with relevant advertisement. This pairing service is provided by third party advertisement hubs, which facilitates real-time bidding for advertisers._uetsid1st1 dayCollects data on visitor behaviour from multiple websites, in order to present more relevant advertisements -This also allows the website to limit the number of times that they are shown the same advertisement._uetsid1stPersistentUsed to track visitors on multiple websites, in order to present relevant advertisements based on the visitor's preferences._uetsid_exp1stPersistentContains the expiry-date for the cookie with corresponding name.ATN3rd2 yearsTargets ads based on behavioural profiling and geographical location.dw_dnt1stSessionCollects information on user preferences and/or interaction with web-campaign content -This is used on CRM-campaign-platform used by website owners for promoting events or products.dwsid1stSessionThis cookie is set to count the number of times a specific visitor is shown a specific ad – the cookie enables the advertisers to differentiate the specific ads shown and thereby making the advertising more efficient.eng_mt1stPersistentTracks the conversion rate between the user and the advertisement banners on the website -This serves to optimise the relevance of the advertisements on the website.https://cx.atdmt.com/3rdSessionSets a unique ID for the visitor, that allows third party advertisers to target the visitor with relevant advertisement. This pairing service is provided by third party advertisement hubs, which facilitates real-time bidding for advertisers.icts3rd1 yearPresents the user with relevant content and advertisement. The service is provided by third-party advertisement hubs, which facilitate real-time bidding for advertisers.icts3rd1 yearCollects data on user behaviour and interaction in order to optimize the website and make advertisement on the website more relevant.IDE3rd1 yearUsed by Google DoubleClick to register and report the website user's actions after viewing or clicking one the advertiser's ads with the purpose of measuring the efficacy of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user.MUID3rd1 yearUsed widely by Microsoft as a unique user ID. The cookie enables user tracking by synchronizing the ID across many Microsoft domains.pagead/1p-user-list/#3rdSessionUsed for Advertisingpxrc3rd2 monthsThis cookie registers data on the visitor. The information is used to optimize advertisement relevance.rlas33rd1 yearCollects visitor data related to the user's visits to the website, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded, with the purpose of displaying targeted ads.t_gid3rd1 yearThis cookie assigns a specific visitor ID, when the visitor interacts with ads or content from the website this allows the website to target the visitor with similar ads or content.taboola global:user-id1stPersistentSets a unique ID for the visitor, that allows third party advertisers to target the visitor with relevant advertisement. This pairing service is provided by third party advertisement hubs, which facilitates real-time bidding for advertisers.taboola_session_id1stSessionThis cookie is used to collect information on a visitor. This information will become an ID string with information on a specific visitor – ID information strings can be used to target groups with similar preferences, or can be used by third party domains or ad-exchanges.test_cookie3rd1 dayUsed to check if the user's browser supports cookies.trctestcookie1stSessionDetects whether partner data synchronization is functioning and currently running -This function sends user data between third-party advertising companies for the purpose of targeted advertisements.utag_main3rd1 yearUsed by Tealium Tag Manager to store a unique visitor ID, a session ID and to persist data about the visitor's interaction with the website, e.g. last page viewed._uetvid1st16 daysUsed for Advertising_uetvid_exp1stPersistentUsed for Advertising1296566:session-data1stPersistentUsed for Advertising14c9e0fdbc334029b05ddf9973bbb96f/eu_tag3rdSessionUsed for Advertisingadadvisor.gif3rdSessionUsed for Advertisingapi/v1/metrics/experience/9wUPeVGr/events.png3rdSessionUsed for Advertisingbc-modcloth#userLifeTime1stPersistentUsed for AdvertisingbluecoreNV1st1 yearUsed for AdvertisingbluecoreSiteALP1stPersistentUsed for AdvertisingbluecoreSiteFirstVisit1stSessionUsed for AdvertisingbluecoreSiteT1stPersistentUsed for AdvertisingbluecoreSiteVisit1stPersistentUsed for Advertisingcuid3rd1 yearUsed for AdvertisinggetSessionStorage1stPersistentUsed for Advertisingku1-sid1stSessionUsed for Advertisingku1-vid1st527 daysUsed for Advertisingku3-vid3rd539 daysUsed for Advertisingmt.v1st5 yearsUsed for Advertisingorder_count_incrementer1st1 dayUsed for Advertisingppid3rdPersistentUsed for Advertisingset3rdSessionUsed for Advertisingstc1204261st1 yearUsed for AdvertisingSteelhouse1st29021 daysUsed for AdvertisingX-AB3rd1 dayUsed for AdvertisingSocial media cookiesCookie NameFirst or Third Party CookiePersistent or Session CookieCookie Purpose__rmco1stPersistentNecessary for the implementation of Instagram picture-gallery onto the website._fbp3rd3 monthsUsed by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers._pin_unauth3rd1 yearUsed by Pinterest to track the usage of services.fr3rd3 monthsUsed by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers.tr3rdSessionUsed by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers.v33rdSessionUsed by Pinterest to track the usage of services._pinterest_ct_ua3rd1 yearUnclassified CHANGESInformation about the cookies used by us may be updated from time to time, so please check back on a regular basis for any changes.
New cookies may be added to the tables above but the types of cookies used on our site will fall within one of the categories of: strictly necessary; analytics; functionality; advertising; and social media.The last modification date of this document is shown at the bottom of this page. QUESTIONSIf you have any questions about this cookie policy, please contact us by email at support@modcloth.com.This cookie policy was last modified September 2020.
